那是什么？
What was that?
什么都没有
Nothing.
好吧，给我一点提示
Okay, just give me one little hint.
不，不要暗示
No, no hints.
我们就快到了
We're almost there.
好了，我要把这个脱了
Okay, I'm going to take this off.
不，不，不
No, no, no.
嘿，你说你喜欢惊喜
Hey, you said you like surprises.
是的，我喜欢
Yeah, I do.
当我知道它们是什么的时候
When I know what they are.
你会喜欢的
You're going to love it.
的承诺
Promise.
哦,是的
Oh, yeah.
我已经很喜欢这里的景色了
I already love the view.
哈哈
Ha ha.
你好
Hello.
好了，我们到了
All right, here we are.
小心脚下，小心脚下
Watch your step, watch your step.
我看不见
I can't see.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
前进,停止
Forward, stop.
我要把它摘下来
I'm taking it off.
现在
Now.
你在开玩笑吧？
Are you kidding?
如何?
How?
我都不知道这里还开着
I didn't even know this place was open
然而
yet.
帮了些忙，让我们上了
Pulled some favors and got us on the
首演名单
list for opening night.
哦!
Oh!
你看起来很丑
You look really ugly.
哇,嗯…
Wow, uh...
你确定我穿得合适吗？
Are you sure I'm dressed all right?
你看起来气色很好
You look like a million bucks.
来吧
Come on.
嘿!
Hey!
不要从喷泉里偷硬币
Don't steal coins from the fountain.
这是坏运气
It's bad luck.
对不起,先生
Sorry sir.
继续
Go on.
微笑
Smile.
你好,先生
Hello, sir.
你想要一张照片吗？
Would you like a photo?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
大家注意脚下
Watch your step, everyone.
你要来吗?
You coming?
嗯,我们……
Uh, we'll...
坐下一个
take the next one.
得了吧
Aw, come on.
我们可以给你安排时间
We can fit you in.
谢谢
Thanks.
上升
Going up.
哦，对不起
Oh, excuse me.
抱歉，它有时会这样
Sorry, it does that sometimes.
啊!
Ah!
关于斯卡维塔的一些趣事
Some fun facts about the Scadvey Tower.
它有494英尺高，重量超过9英尺
It's 494 feet tall and weighs over 9
000吨
,000 tons.
它是由钢和钢筋混凝土建造的
It's made of steel and reinforced concrete and
玻璃
glass.
更令人印象深刻的是，整个项目
And even more impressive, the entire project was
提前5个月完工
completed five months ahead of schedule.
这是一件好事吗？
Is that a good thing?
我怎么跟你说的？
What'd I tell you?
南希吗?
Nancy?
是吗?
Yes?
我能为您效劳吗？
May I help you?
我们预订了房间
We have a reservation.
坎贝尔
Campbell.
哦，很抱歉，我们已经客满了
Oh, I'm sorry, but we're already over capacity
首演之夜
for opening night.
我们不能接待你
We cannot accommodate you.
如果你不介意的话，请靠边站
If you wouldn't mind just stepping aside.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
没关系
It's okay.
我和杰克解决了
I worked it out with Jake.
他在这儿吗？
Is he here?
我可以说……
I could speak...
我们今天早上放杰克走了
We let Jake go this morning.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
这是怎么呢？
What's going on?
1秒
One second.
先生，您是一位非常重要的人物
Sir, you're a very important man.
也许你能帮我
Maybe you could help me out.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
请
Please.
你把我撕碎了
You're tearing me apart.
对不起，我帮不了你
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
如果你不介意的话
If you wouldn't mind.
富勒先生，很高兴见到你
Oh, Mr. Fuller, how nice to see you.
我们为您准备了一张漂亮的桌子
We have a lovely table for you.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我们去酒吧吧
Let's go to the bar.
怎么啦？
What?
表现自然
Act natural.
看看这景色
Look at the view.
怎么啦？
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
你恐高？
You're scared of heights?
不，我只是…
No, I'm just...
我只是从来没来过这么高的地方
I've just never been this high up before.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
今晚真是一场灾难
This night's turning into such a disaster.
我真的想让它完美
I really wanted it to be perfect.
嘿
Hey.
这是完美的
It is perfect.
因为我和你在一起
Because I'm with you.
啊
Ah.
你没事吧?
You okay?
我想我能活下来
I think I'll live.
是吗?
Yeah?
嘿，看，免费的香槟
Hey, look, free champagne.
那是我最喜欢的一种
That's my favorite kind.
要我骑上去吗？
Want me to ride up?
好吧
Okay.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
对不起，请问女洗手间在哪里？
Excuse me, where's the ladies' room?
舞池的另一边
Other side of the dance floor.
我从我得到的天空中坠落
And I tumbled from the sky I got
感觉我正在坠入爱河爱上你
to feeling I'm a-falling Loving you's the
原因，原因
reason why The reason
为什么你就是为什么谢谢你
why You're the reason why Thank you.
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
嗨,亲爱的
Hi, sweetie.
一切都还好吗？
Is everything all right?
我很好，谢谢
I'm fine, thank you.
你怀孕多久了？
How far along are you?
怎么啦？
What?
哦，不，我没有
Oh, no, I'm not.
我不太清楚
I don't know exactly.
也许一两个月
Maybe one or two months.
这是个好消息
That's wonderful news.
不是吗?
Isn't it?
我还没告诉我男朋友
I haven't told my boyfriend yet.
他爱你吗？
Does he love you?
是
Yes.
那他就不会放手
Then he won't let go.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
当然可以
Of course.
再见
Bye.
好了，快结束了
Okay, it's almost over.
哦
Oh.
嘿,什么?
Hey, what?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
是的
Yeah.
我想是的
I think so.
来吧
Come on.
我们去呼吸点新鲜空气吧
Let's get some fresh air.
我真的需要……
I really need to...
对不起，我想…
I'm sorry, I wanted to...
你先来
You go first.
好吧
Okay.
我本想在晚餐时说的，
I was going to do this at dinner,
但是既然我们有这个观点…
but seeing as we have this view...
嘿，别扔那枚硬币
Hey, don't throw that penny.
你会杀人的
You could kill somebody.
哦，我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
当然可以
Of course.
胖的屁股
Fat ass.
嗯…
Um...
过去的几年真是太神奇了
These past few years have been absolutely magical.
那是…
And that's, uh...
那都是因为你
That's because of you.
爱瑞丝，我想用剩下的时间
Iris, I want to spend the rest of
我与你共度一生
my life with you.
你的意思是……
You mean...
与我们?
With us?
怎么啦？
What?
对不起
Sorry.
我…
I...
我是世界上最幸运的人
I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
怎么啦？
What?
你不难过吗？
You're not upset?
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
不，这是……
No, this is...
这太不可思议了
This is incredible.
真的吗?
Really?
我们要组建一个家庭
We're going to start a family.
嗯,所以…
Um, so...
你会吗?
Will you?
哦,是的
Oh, yes.
是不是太紧了？
Is it too tight?
它是完美的
It's perfect.
嘿，我们去庆祝一下吧
Hey, let's go celebrate.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
那就意味着我的眼睛会…
That has to mean my eyes will...
孩子第一次!
Children first!
到
To the
电梯!
elevator!
动!
Move!
哦,不
Oh no.
的帮助
Help.
哦，我马上就到
Oh, I'll be right there.
Aghhhh !
Aghhhh!
帮帮我!
Help me!
我知道向量乘法很吓人，但是
Well, I realize vector multiplication is scary, but
没那么可怕
it's not that scary.
好了，今天就到这里
Alright, that's it for today.
我们将开始准备下周的期末考试
We'll start prepping for the final next week.
雷耶斯女士，我们得谈谈
Ms. Reyes, we need to talk.
我们是一家人，不是吗？
We're a family, aren't we?
别把那枚硬币从空中扔出去
Don't throw that penny out of the air.
它可能会害死人
It could kill someone.
所有人都会死！
Everyone's gonna die!
这个梦毁了我的生活
This dream is ruining my life.
我也是
Mine too.
每天晚上，斯蒂芬
Every night, Steph.
天啊，我根本睡不着
God, I'm not getting any sleep.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我能告诉你一件事吗？
Um, can I tell you something?
是啊，怎么了？
Yeah, what's up?
我梦中的女人，她的名字
So, the woman in my dream, her name
是爱瑞丝，对吧？
is Iris, right?
好吧
Okay.
那是我祖母的名字
That was my grandmother's name.
我，我想我梦到她了
I, uh, I think I'm dreaming about her.
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
是的
Yeah.
问题是，我根本没见过她
The thing is, I never even met her.
我都不知道她是不是还活着
I don't even know if she's alive.
好吧，那你要么回家去问问
Okay, well, either go home and find out
关于奶奶的事，希望能阻止梦，
about Grandma and hope that stops the dreams,
或者留在这里，在睡梦中死去，
or stay here and die in your sleep,
为真实的
for real.
因为我会杀了你
Because I will murder you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧，好吧
Yeah, yeah, okay.
爱你!
Love you!
我也爱你
Love you too.
回家了
Go home.
是的
Yeah.
安静地
Quietly.
史蒂芬妮
Steph.
嘿，她来了
Hey, there she is.
嗨,爸爸
Hey, Dad.
欢迎回家，亲爱的
Welcome home, sweetie.
很高兴你能来
So glad you're here.
是啊，我也是
Yeah, me too.
我很想你
I miss you so much.
我知道
I know.
很高兴见到你
So great to see you.
谢谢，谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
拿去吧
Take that for you.
嘿,抱歉
Hey, sorry.
查理刚才占用了你的房间
Charlie took your room a while ago, and
我的文件在他房间里，所以我
my files are in his room, so I
给你编了个拔枪的动作
made up the pull-out for you.
可以吗？
Is that okay?
是啊，是啊，听起来完全没问题
Yeah, yeah, no, that sounds totally fine.
嘿，我们还有那盒
Hey, do we still have that box of
妈妈的旧东西？
Mom's old stuff?
里面有一些照片，像地址簿，
It had some photos, like an address book,
里面有电话号码
phone numbers in it.
你为什么想要这个？
Why do you want that?
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
我只是觉得它就在我身边
I just thought I saw it lying around
在这里某个地方
here somewhere.
斯蒂芬妮，怎么了？
Stephanie, what's going on?
好吧，这听起来真的，真的
Okay, this is going to sound really, really
很奇怪，但我得找到妈妈的
weird, but I just need to find Mom's
妈妈,虹膜
mom, Iris.
嗯…
Uh...
好吧，确实很奇怪
Okay, yeah, that is weird.
你知道，我把它们都去掉了
And you know, I got rid of those
几年前，妈妈离开后
boxes years ago, after Mom left.
哦，嗨，查理
Oh, hi, Charlie.
嘿
Hey.
嗨，斯蒂芬
Um, hi, Steph.
你好吗？
How are you?
见到你真高兴
It's so nice to see you.
是的,当然
Yeah, sure.
你要去考辛斯家吗？
Uh, you going to the Cousins?
哇,现在?
Whoa, now?
虎克，你妹妹，刚回来
Hook, your sister, just got home.
我想我们可以…
I thought we could...
事实上，你知道吗？
Actually, you know what?
我可以开车送你
I can drive you.
反正我也想看看他们
I was wanting to see them anyways.
它很好
It's fine.
嘿，如果你要去看你的表亲，
Hey, if you're going to see your cousins,
别跟霍华德叔叔说爱瑞丝的事
please don't talk about Iris to Uncle Howard.
是的
Yeah.
是的，没问题
Yeah, no problem.
好吧
All right.
再见，爱你
Bye, love you.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
查理?
Charlie?
查理，你能把这些拿出来吗？
Charlie, can you just take these out, please?
我想和你谈谈
I'm trying to talk to you.
你怎么了？
What's your problem?
怎么啦？
What?
我只是…
I just...
你一直都没说什么
You haven't said anything this entire time.
嗯…
Well...
斯蒂芬，你怎么来了？
Steph, why are you here?
我是说，你只在假期才回家
I mean, you only come home for holidays.
好吧，我得告诉你件事，但是
Okay, I have to tell you something, but
你得保证不告诉爸爸
you have to promise not to tell Dad.
你怀孕了吗？
Are you pregnant?
不，我没有怀孕，查理
No, I'm not pregnant, Charlie.
我不知道
I don't know.
你为什么要…
Why would you even...
这不是……
That's not...
我是说，你在上大学
I mean, you're in college.
你能保证你不会说出去吗
Can you just promise me you won't tell
爸爸?
Dad?
我为什么要告诉爸爸？
Why would I tell Dad?
这很严重，查理
It's serious, Charlie.
好吧
All right.
Okay.
我在留校察看
I am on academic probation.
哇
Whoa.
停止笑
Stop laughing.
如果我的成绩不提高……
If I don't get my grades up...
这是一个重要的时刻
This is kind of a big moment for
我
me.
这有点好笑
This is kind of funny.
A
Straight A's.
你是班长
You're a class president.
错过优秀毕业生
Miss Valedictorian.
查理，这一点都不好笑
Charlie, it's not funny.
如果我的成绩不提高，我
If I don't get my grades up, I
就会失去奖学金
will lose my scholarship.
哦
Oh.
我发出嗡嗡声
I buzzed.
对不起
Sorry.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我睡不着
I can't sleep.
每次我闭上眼睛，我都会
Every time I close my eyes, I have
这个关于爱瑞丝的噩梦，我们的祖母
this same recurring nightmare about Iris, our grandmother.
我不…
I don't...
我是说，这肯定有什么意义
I mean, it has to mean something.
我不知道
I don't know.
我做奇怪的梦
I dream weird things.
我梦见一只热狗把我吃了
I dreamed a hot dog ate me last
的夜晚
night.
怎么啦？
What?
就像热狗在吃我
Like, the hot dog was eating me.
好吧
Okay.
老兄，你能做点什么吗？
Dude, can you just do something?
伙计，冷静点
Dude, calm down.
稍微动一下
Just move a little bit.
我不能停在这些在线信息上
I can't pause over these online messages.
我得看看下面
I have to look under these.
你能帮我个忙吗？
Can you do me a kindness?
滚蛋
Fuck off.
你还记得上次发生了什么吗？
Do you remember what happened last time?
这是一场排位赛
It's a ranked match.
这是怎么呢？
What's going on?
我找不到帕科
I can't find Paco.
老兄,一遍吗?
Dude, again?
帕科是谁?
Who's Paco?
不可能
No way.
嘿，嘿，老兄
Hey, hey, cuz.
我的天啊
Oh my gosh.
你能帮我们找找吗？
Hey, can you help us look?
走路的时候注意脚下
And just watch your feet when you're stepping.
是的，是的，当然
Yeah, yeah, sure.
我只是…
I just...
我得先和你爸爸谈谈
I gotta talk to your dad first.
你他妈的在家里干什么？
The fuck are you doing home?
老兄，她他妈已经退学了
Oh, dude, she's fucking out of school.
嘿
Hey.
欢迎加入我们
Welcome to the club.
埃里克，老兄，你找过吗？
Eric, dude, have you looked anywhere?
帕科不在楼上
Paco's not upstairs.
哦，但是看看谁来了
Oh, but look who's down here.
你好,茱莉亚
Hi, Julia.
我的天啊
Oh my gosh.
你还好吗？
How you been?
查理
Charlie.
朱尔斯
Jules.
这是我的小罗密欧
There's my little Romeo.
等等，你跟珍妮的求婚怎么样
So, wait, how did the promposal with Jenny
去了?
go?
老兄，她答应了
Dude, she said yes.
我的天啊
Oh my God.
停止
Stop.
好的,等待
Okay, wait.
谁，谁是珍妮？
Who's, uh, who's Jenny?
他在《初级救生员》里认识她的
Oh, he met her in Junior Lifeguards.
初级救生员
Junior Lifeguards.
查理，我没有…
Charlie, I didn't...
我不知道你在拍《初级救生员》
I didn't know you were doing Junior Lifeguards.
好吧
Okay.
那你打算穿什么？
So what are you gonna wear?
呃，就简单点吧
Uh, just gonna keep it simple.
没有黑色运动上衣
No black blazer.
好吧
Okay.
但是…
But...
对，对，对，对
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
但要有个有趣的蝴蝶结
But with, like, a fun bow.
我喜欢它
I like it.
停!
Stop!
斯蒂芬妮!
Stephanie!
我的天啊
Oh my gosh.
嗨,蜂蜜
Hi, honey.
嗨，我是布伦达
Hi, I'm Brenda.
你要在这里待多久？
How long are you here for?
不长
Uh, not long.
霍华德叔叔在吗？
Uh, is, is Uncle Howard around?
是的，是的，他在后面
Yeah, yeah, he's out back.
我去找他
I'll get him.
霍华德!
Howard!
斯蒂芬妮在这里
Stephanie's here.
进来
Come in.
好了
Great.
你看起来有点累
You look a little tired.
一切都还好吗？
Is everything okay?
哦
Oh.
斯蒂芬妮!
Stephanie!
看看你！
Look at you!
过来，过来
Come here, come here.
哦,亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
见到你真是太好了
Oh, it's so good to see you.
嘿，你饿吗？
Hey, are you hungry?
我只是想做点午餐
I was just gonna make some lunch.
呃，不，实际上
Uh, no, actually.
我来这里是因为我想
Uh, I came here because I wanted to
跟你谈谈你妈妈，爱瑞丝
talk to you about your mother, Iris.
我知道你不喜欢谈论
I know you don't like to talk about
她的
her.
没什么可说的
There's not much to tell.
嘿，孩子们，快点，吃午饭！
Hey, kids, come on, lunch!
只是我一直，我一直
It's just that I've been, I've been having
关于她的噩梦反复出现
this recurring nightmare about her.
亲爱的，可能只是压力太大了
Oh, honey, it's probably just stress.
你应该试试褪黑素
You should try melatonin.
好吧，但奇怪的是，我一直
Okay, but the weird thing is, I've been
梦想着一个真正的地方，从50岁开始
dreaming about a real place from, from 50
年前的事了
years ago.
那是一家叫天景的餐厅
It was, like, a restaurant called The Skyview.
你知道是什么吗？
You know what it is?
爱瑞丝跟你说过吗？
Did, did Iris tell you about it?
她，她说了什么？
Uh, what did, what did she say?
她说什么了吗？
Did, did she say anything?
也许，也许如果我能和
Um, maybe, maybe if I could talk to
她的
her...
和谁谈？
Talk to who?
斯蒂芬梦到爱瑞丝奶奶了
Uh, Steph is dreaming about Grandma Iris.
心理奶奶吗?
Psycho granny?
我以为她死了
I thought she was dead.
对我们来说她已经死了
Well, she's dead to us.
史黛菲，爱瑞丝·坎贝尔精神非常不正常
Stephie, Iris Campbell is a very deeply disturbed
女人
woman.
故事结束了
End of story.
听着，如果我能跟她谈谈，
Look, if I could just talk to her,
然后，也许，也许我能得到这些
then, then maybe, maybe I can get these
梦想要停止
dreams to stop.
斯蒂芬，放下吧
Steph, just drop it.
我不明白
I don't get it.
发生了什么这么糟糕的事？
What, what happened that was so bad?
首先，是她让你
For one thing, she's the reason that your
妈妈真是一团糟
mother's so screwed up.
怎么啦？
What?
听着，我只是不想谈
Look, I just don't want to talk about
再这样了，好吗？
this anymore, okay?
霍华德叔叔，求你了，我只想知道
Uncle Howard, please, I just need to know.
史黛菲，父亲死后，爱瑞丝
Look, Stephie, after our father died, Iris just
厉声说
snapped.
她，她不让我们上学
She, she wouldn't let us go to school.
她把我们锁在屋子里
She locked us inside the house.
她痴迷于我们所有可怕的方式
She obsessed about all the horrific ways we
可能会死
could die.
最后情况变得很糟糕，我是说
And eventually it got so bad, I mean
太糟糕了，政府介入了
so bad, that the state came in and
他们把我和你妈妈带走了
they took your mother and I away from
她的
her.
但事情并没有就此结束
But it didn't end there.
她，她在寄养中心跟踪我们
She, she tracked us all through foster care.
孩子们出生后，她开始
And when the kids were born, she started
给我们寄来这些满是垃圾的信
sending us these horrible letters that were full
讣告和这些令人不安的死者照片
of obituaries and these disturbing pictures of dead
的身体
bodies.
我们得搬家，所以她联系不上
We had to move, so she couldn't contact
我们了
us anymore.
那么，你还有
So, uh, do you still have any of
那些信呢？
those letters, though?
我…
I...
史黛菲，听我说
Stephie, listen to me.
那个女人是个病态的危险人物
That woman is a sick and dangerous person.
为了你们的健康和安全，
And for your well-being and your safety,
离她远点
stay the hell away from her.
我相信你
I believe you.
我找到了帕科
I found Paco.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
我相信他会很乐意参加
I'm sure he'd love to be in the
现在就在客厅
living room right now.
不可能
No way.
来吧，伙计们，我们走
Come on, guys, let's go.
他是怎么进去的？
How did he even get in there?
我需要你的帮助
I need you to help me.
你听到你叔叔的话了
You heard your uncle.
随它去吧
Just let it go.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我的整个人生都毁了，就因为
My whole life is falling apart because of
这一梦想
this dream.
不仅如此，我觉得，我
And not only that, I feel like, I
我觉得我快要疯了
feel like I'm losing my mind.
求你了，只有你能
Please, you are the only person who can
帮助我
help me.
霍华德不会原谅我的，如果我把
Howard would never forgive me if I put
你和爱瑞丝有联系吗
you in touch with Iris.
请
Please.
不管你做什么，别往里看
Whatever you do, do not look in the
餐厅橱柜最下面的抽屉
bottom drawer of the dining room cabinet.
你好，我来找爱瑞丝·坎贝尔
Hi, um, I'm here to see Iris Campbell.
你没看到征兆吗？
Did you not see the signs?
嗯，嗯，是的，我说了，但是…
Uh, uh, yeah, yes, I did, but...
那就给我滚出去
Then get the fuck out of here.
没有游客
No visitors.
我是你的孙女
I'm your granddaughter.
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie.
掏空口袋
Empty your pockets.
电话，钥匙，所有东西
Phone, keys, everything.
好吧，我不危险
Well, I'm not dangerous.
我怕的不是你
It's not you I'm afraid of.
嗯…
Uh...
慢慢进来
Come in slowly.
把门关上
Shut the door.
快，快，快
Quick, quick, quick.
不要动
Don't move.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
真的是你
It really is you.
我能在你身上看到你母亲的影子
I can see your mother in you.
嗨，我是斯蒂芬妮
Hi, I'm Stephanie.
停，停，不要
Stop, stop, don't.
移动
Move.
除非我告诉你
Not until I tell you.
你想骗我，是吗？
Trying to trick me, aren't you?
让我放松警惕
Getting me to let my guard down.
我…
I...
坐下
Sit.
好吧，坐下
Okay, um, sit.
就是这样
That's it.
达琳怎么样了？
So, how is Darlene?
你妈妈，好吗？
Your mom, okay?
哦，不，我不知道
Oh, uh, no, I don't know.
她在我十岁的时候离开了，
She, uh, she left when I was ten,
所以我们再也见不到她了
so we don't see her anymore.
哦
Oh.
但你看到了我的信，所以你才
But you saw my letters, that's why you're
在这里,对吗?
here, right?
否
No.
其实我来这是因为我在做梦
Um, I'm actually here because I've been dreaming
关于天空的景色
about the sky view.
哦
Oh.
是的
Yeah.
是啊，过去两天每晚都是
Yeah, every single night for the past two
几个月来，还是同一个梦
months, it's the same dream.
在里面，你是在约会，但是
In it, you're on a date, but then
舞池破了，然后就
the dance floor breaks, and then there's an
爆炸，然后你…
explosion, and then you...
倒下，死去
Fall and die.
是的
Yeah.
是的，每个人都会死
Yeah, everyone dies.
这不仅仅是你的梦想
It wasn't just your dream.
这是我的预感
It was my premonition.
几年前，在天空的景色中，我得到了
Years ago, at the sky view, I got
一瞥未来，看到了什么
a glimpse into the future and saw what
死亡即将来临
death was about to do.
我本打算晚饭时说的，但是
I was gonna do this at dinner, but
既然我们有这个观点……
seeing as we have this view...
嘿，别扔那枚硬币
Hey, don't throw that penny.
你会杀人的
You could kill somebody.
哦，我当然很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry, of course.
过去的两年真是太神奇了，
These past two years have been absolutely magical,
这都是因为你
and that's all because of you.
不不不，我…
No, no, no, no, I...
这不对，我…
This isn't right, I...
那是否定的吗？
Is that a no?
每个人都会死
Everyone's going to die.
整栋楼都要倒了
The whole building is going to come down
和…
and...
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
一分钱
The penny.
虹膜?
Iris?
给我
Give me that.
怎么回事，女士？
What the hell, lady?
把它给我！
Give it to me!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你他妈有什么毛病？
What the fuck is wrong with you?
虹膜?
Iris?
不玩!
Don't play!
所有人都得离开舞池！
Everyone needs to get off the dance floor!
玻璃杯要碎了！
The glass is about to break!
所有人现在都得下车！
Everyone needs to get off now!
等待,不!
Wait, no!
离开舞池！
Get off the dance floor!
虹膜!
Iris!
你得下车！
You need to get off!
下车!
Get off!
那晚我救了很多人的命
I saved a lot of lives that night.
那些本不该被拯救的生命
Lives that were never meant to be saved.
在那之后他们关闭了餐厅
They closed the restaurant after that.
说它需要额外的装修
Said it needed additional renovations.
但它从未重新开放
But it never reopened.
最后他们把它拆掉了
Eventually they tore it down.
等等，所以你阻止了这场灾难？
Wait, so you stopped the disaster?
是
Yes.
但死神不喜欢你做爱
But death doesn't like it when you fuck
他的计划
with his plans.
所以几年之后他又回来了
So over the years he came back.
他杀了所有在场的人
And he killed everyone who was there that
的夜晚
night.
包括我的保罗
Including my Paul.
等等，等一下
Wait, wait a minute.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你是…
Did you...
你是说死神回来了？
Did you say death came back?
他是个无情的混蛋
He's a relentless son of a bitch.
不完成任务他是不会罢休的
Won't stop till he finishes the job.
但我教会了自己如何看待他
But I taught myself how to see him
来了
coming.
预测他的一举一动
To anticipate his every move.
多年来一直在阻止他
Been keeping him at bay for years now.
现在他抓住我了
And now he's got me.
癌症
Cancer.
相信这些屁话？
Believe that shit?
对不起
Sorry.
两个月前得到了诊断
Got the diagnosis two months ago.
等等，那是我开始做梦的时候
Wait, that's when I started having my dream.
看到了吗?
See?
这是一个征兆
It's a sign.
好吧，但我为什么要梦到什么
Okay, but why am I dreaming about what
你看到了吗?
you saw?
也许我的癌症把我的预感传给了
Maybe my cancer passed my premonition on to
你
you.
也许这是命运疯狂的幽默感
Maybe it's fate's demented sense of humor.
谁知道呢？
Who the hell knows?
重要的是，当宇宙说话的时候
What matters is that when the universe speaks
你注意了
you pay attention.
我看见你了，你个混蛋
I see you, you fuck.
嗯…
Um...
谁……
Who...
你在跟谁说话？
who are you talking to?
死亡
Death.
他觉得我因为你在这里而分心了
He thinks I'm distracted because you're here.
我得教你这一切
I have to teach you everything in this
书
book.
学习基本知识需要一些时间
It'll take some time to learn the basics.
所以你得待在这里
So you'll need to stay here.
呆在这里吗?
Stay here?
外面的世界太危险了
The outside world is too dangerous.
我都20年没出门了
I haven't stepped out there in 20 years.
在这里，我们很安全
In here, we can be safe.
哦
Oh.
看到了吗?
See that?
是的
Yeah.
这是我所有的研究
This is all my research.
我毕生的事业
My life's work.
看,我…
Look, I'm...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我…
I...
我不能……
I can't...
我不能待在这里
I can't stay here.
我…
I...
我得回学校了
I have to get back to school.
但是，你知道，我会…
But, you know, I'll...
我会回来拜访你的
I'll come back and I'll visit.
不!
No!
我病了!
I'm sick!
我活不了那么久了
I won't be alive that long.
你不能走
You can't leave.
你还不明白吗？
Don't you see?
我们家就要死了
Death is coming for our family.
嗯…
Uh...
你不相信我？
You don't believe me?
不,我……
No, I...
我…
I'm...
我认为……
I think...
我想我犯了一个错误
I think I made a mistake.
我认为……
I think it...
我想可能只是…
I think it was probably just...
一个梦
a dream.
不,等等!
No, wait!
至少拿着这本书！
At least take the book!
听着，我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
我不该来这里的
I shouldn't have come here.
这本书是救命稻草
This book is a lifeline.
它会告诉你需要的一切
It will show you everything you need to
知道如何保护家人的安全
know to keep our family safe.
你还是不相信我？
You still don't believe me?
退一步
Step back.
怎么啦？
What?
为什么?
Why?
眼见为实
Seeing is believing.
不!
No!
嘿,史蒂芬
Hey, Steph.
她的脸在我面前炸开了
Her face really exploded right in front of
你
you.
那是不是……
Is that like...
我…
I'm...
别烦她
Just leave her alone.
是我的错，斯蒂芬
It's my bad, Steph.
我只是好奇
I'm just curious.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗？
How are you holding up?
是的
Yeah.
对不起，叔叔帮了忙
I'm sorry Uncle helped.
爱瑞丝的事你是对的
You were right about Iris.
我从来没有……
I never...
我不应该去那里
I never should have went there.
亲爱的，没必要道歉
Honey, there's no need to apologize.
我很抱歉让你经历这一切
I'm so sorry you had to go through
那
that.
她死前对我说了些话
She said something to me before she died.
她说我们家就要死了
She said death was coming for our family.
这是……
That's...
这很疯狂，对吧？
That's crazy, right?
我的天啊
Oh my God.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我给她发了邮件
I emailed her.
我只是觉得她不会出现
I just didn't think she'd show up.
来吧
Come on.
你知道吗？
You know what?
嗯…
Um...
演示吗?
Demo?
是的
Yeah.
达琳!
Darlene!
哇
Wow.
嗯…
Um...
我可以回来的
I can come back.
哦，别傻了
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
来吧
Come on.
给我下来
Get down here.
到这里来
Come here.
你觉得她会来烧烤吗？
Think she'll come to the barbecue?
史蒂芬,嘿
Steph, hey.
如果她要去霍华德叔叔家，那么
If she's going to Uncle Howard's house, then
我不是
I'm not.
你可以搭爸爸的车
You can get a ride with Dad.
你都不打算和她谈谈吗？
You're not even going to talk to her?
来吧
Come on.
你不像我这么记得她
You don't remember her like I do.
给她一个机会
Just give her a chance.
为什么?
Why?
查理，她抛弃了我们，现在她滚了
Charlie, she abandoned us and now she rolls
在这里吗?
in here?
这么多年过去了，我想演戏
After all these years and wants to act
就像什么都没发生一样？
like nothing happened?
因为他会这么做
Because he would do that.
对吧?
Right?
等等,什么?
Wait, what?
什么都没有
Nothing.
否
No.
这是什么意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
我给你打了很多次电话
I tried calling you so many times.
和什么都没有
And nothing.
茱莉亚也一样
Same with Julia.
你们曾经是最好的朋友
You used to be best friends.
你都不说话了
You don't even talk anymore.
好吧
Okay.
我很抱歉
Well, I'm sorry.
我…
I...
我只是最近几次分心了
I've just been distracted the last couple of
几个月就因为这个噩梦
months because of this nightmare.
在那之前呢？
What about before that?
自从你走后就一直是这样
It's been like this ever since you left.
你在生妈妈的气，但你没有
You're mad at Mom, but you haven't been
周围
around either.
我不像她
I'm not like her.
好吧?
Okay?
我没疯
I'm not crazy.
是的，你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
你没疯
You're not crazy.
你根本不在乎
You just don't care.
好吧
All right.
现在你明白了
Now you got it.
小心碎片
Watch out for splinters.
嘿，她来了
Hey, there she is.
嘿
Hey.
到这里来
Come here.
我很高兴你来了
I'm so glad you made it.
我还以为你不是真的
You know, I didn't think you were actually
马上就来
going to come.
谢谢你邀请我
Thank you for inviting me.
当然可以
Of course.
请进
Come on in.
嘿,每一个人
Hey, everybody.
来吧
Come on.
过来吧
Come on over.
我做了饼干
I made cookies.
太好了
That's great.
我可以试试吗？
Can I try one?
是的，当然
Yes, of course.
这里面有花生酱吗？
Does this have peanut butter?
是的
Yeah.
你想杀我弟弟吗？
Are you trying to kill my brother?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
鲍比的过敏
Bobby's allergic.
是的
Yeah.
我完全忘了
I totally forgot.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
重要的是你在这里
The important thing is that you're here.
鲍比酒保
So, uh, Bobby Bartender.
饮料
Drinks.
到处都是饮料
Drinks all around.
家庭
Family.
你不能选择你想要的
You don't get to pick the one you
得到的
get.
你只需要爱上那个
You just got to love the one that
你有
you got.
我们的母亲，她一个人住，直到
Now, uh, our mother, she lived alone until
她死的那天
the day that she died.
她的死应该是一个提醒
And her death should be a reminder to
我们所有人都要享受生活和消费
all of us to enjoy life and spend
我们在一起的时光
the time that we have together.
因为我们一分钱都拿不回来了
Because we're not going to get any back.
我爱你们
I love you guys.
哇哇哇
Aww.
为此干杯
Cheers to that.
欢呼
Cheers.
嗯
Mmm.
这是强大的
This is strong.
你在里面放了什么？
What did you put in there?
茱莉亚?
Julia?
哦,很酷
Oh, cool.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
里面有个虫子
There's a bug in there.
你的版税
Your royalty.
啊
Ah.
你是谁?
You are?
实际上,是的
Actually, yeah.
我要放弃我的最高职位了
I'm turning in my crowning job.
太好了
That's great.
是的
Yeah.
查理!
Charlie!
上来！
Get up here!
哇!
Whoa!
埃里克
Eric.
妈
Ma.
烧烤的准备
Grill's ready.
介意我和你一起吗？
Mind if I join you?
请坐
Have a seat.
卸下负担
Take the load off.
哦,是的
Oh, yeah.
好了
There we go.
你这里的布置太棒了
It's great, the setup you've got here.
我想让孩子们有个
Well, I wanted the kids to have a
快乐的童年
happy childhood.
不像我认识的一些人
Unlike some people I know.
你不是在说我们吧？
You're not talking about us, are you?
哦,不
Oh, no.
我们有一个美好的童年
We had a great childhood.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
我是说，看看我
I mean, look at me.
我变得很棒
I turned out fabulous.
是的
Yep.
哦
Oh.
霍华德
Howard.
怎么啦？
What?
来吧
Come on.
那是什么？
What is that?
它看起来像一把房门钥匙
It looks like a house key.
我的意思是……
I mean...
来吧
Come on.
你知道我们有空房的
You know we got the spare room.
这肯定比弹跳好多了
And it's got to be better than bouncing
在拖车停车场附近
around trailer parks.
我觉得这不是个好主意
I don't think this is a good idea.
第二次机会永远不会太迟
It's never too late for a second chance.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没有我他们会过得更好
They're better off without me.
捡起
Pick up.
接电话，快点
Pick up, come on.
你发现我了，对吧？
You're onto me, right?
你盯上我了
You're onto me.
让我们看看你的背
Come show us your back
翻转
flip.
怎么啦？
What?
不，不，不
No, no, no.
是啊，拜托，霍华德叔叔
Yeah, come on, Uncle Howard.
拜托，霍华德
Come on, Howard.
霍华德
Howard.
把他抬起来
Up him up.
好了
There you go.
好吧
All right.
开始吧
Here we go.
小心
Watch out.
等待
Wait.
停止
Stop.
哦
Oh.
接得好，阿姨
Nice catch, Auntie.
好吧
All right.
开始吧
Here we go.
好的,爸爸
Okay, Dad.
我们开始吧
Let's do it.
远离那个边缘
Stay away from that edge.
拜托，霍华德叔叔
Come on, Uncle Howard.
开始吧
Here we go.
就像大学一样
Just like college.
那很好
That was nice.
小心,霍华德
Careful, Howard.
我最好把它弄出来
I better get it out of there.
嘿,斯蒂芬妮
Hey, Stephanie.
你做到了
You made it.
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie.
我很高兴你决定来
I'm glad you decided to come.
现在全家人都来了
Now the whole family's here.
是的
Yeah.
我很好
I'm okay.
I'm all right.
哦,很好
Oh, good.
我很好
I'm okay.
没关系
It's okay.
没关系的
It's all right.
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
以前的事都过去了
The former things are passed away.
也没有哀恸，也没有痛苦
Neither shall there be mourning nor pain, and
他要擦去他们的眼泪
he shall wipe away every tear from their
眼睛，死亡将不复存在
eyes, and death shall be no more.
嘿
Hey.
这些东西都去哪了？
Where's all this stuff?
我在爱瑞丝的书里找到了这些文件
I found these papers in Iris' book.
它们是给人民的讣告和文章
They are obituaries and articles for the people
那晚谁在天景酒店
who were at the Skyview on the night
爱瑞丝有预感
that Iris had her premonition.
这些人中的每一个都继续
Each one of these people went on to
以奇怪而混乱的方式死去，
die in some weird and messed up way,
不仅如此，他们都死于
and not only that, they all died in
和艾瑞斯的预感顺序一样
the same order as Iris' premonition.
成百上千的人本该死在那
Hundreds of people were supposed to die that
但艾瑞斯阻止了这场灾难
night, but Iris stopped the disaster.
于是死神一个接一个地回来了
So death came back for them one by
一个
one.
因为有这么多幸存者，所以
Since there were so many survivors, it took
等死亡降临到所有人
years for death to get to all of
但最终还是传染给了爱瑞丝
them, but eventually it got to Iris.
她是最后一个死在
She was the last to die in the
预感
premonition.
是她和一个小男孩，但是
It was her and a little boy, but
她准备好了
she was prepared.
她以一己之力抵挡了几十年的死亡
She single-handedly held off death for decades.
斯蒂芬妮，亲爱的，我觉得这不是
Stephanie, sweetie, I don't think this is the
这正是时候
appropriate time for this.
是啊，我是说，这些都没
Yeah, I mean, none of this even has
跟我们有关的事，对吧？
anything to do with us, right?
我们为什么会在这里？
Why are we even here?
不，就这样
No, that's it.
这和我们有很大关系
It has everything to do with us.
我是说，因为死亡需要很长时间
I mean, because death took so long to
穿过幸存者，穿过这些人
make its way through the survivors, these people
后来有了家庭，他们的家庭
went on to have families, families that they
本不该有
never should have had.
所以死亡也带走了他们
So death took them too.
你看不出来吗？
Don't you see this?
死亡向我们走来，因为我们曾经是
Death is coming for us because we were
不应该存在
never supposed to exist.
好吧，那为什么这个房间里的每个人
Okay, so why everybody in this room is
在死亡名单上？
on death's hit list?
鲍比，斯托克，她是这么说的
Bobby, Stock, that's what she's saying.
不，不，不
No, no, no.
爸爸和布兰达阿姨很安全，因为他们
Dad and Aunt Brenda are safe because they're
不是爱瑞丝的血统
not part of Iris' bloodline.
好吧，按照这种模式，死亡就会到来
Okay, following the pattern, death makes its way
每根树枝都按年龄排列
down each branch by age.
因为霍华德叔叔是老大，所以
So because Uncle Howard was the oldest, it'll
先从他的家人开始，也就是说埃里克，你
start with his family first, meaning Eric, you're
下一个
next.
去你妈的
Go fuck yourself.
然后是茱莉亚，然后是鲍比
Then it'll go for Julia, then Bobby.
然后它会来找我们的分支，从
Then it'll come for our branch, starting with
达琳，然后是我，查理
Darlene, then me, then Charlie.
查理，你相信吗？
Charlie, you buying this?
我不知道
I don't know.
这太乱了
This is so messed up.
你把我们爸爸的死变成了
I mean, you're turning our dad's death into
某种该死的阴谋论
some kind of fucked-up conspiracy theory.
你怎么了？
What is wrong with you?
不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
这不是阴谋论
It's not, it's not a conspiracy theory.
工厂,足够了
Fab, enough.
我们都会死的
We're all gonna die.
停止
Stop.
我再也听不下去了
I can't listen to this for one more
分钟
minute.
那个疯女人的胡言乱语已经够让人痛苦的了
That crazy woman's nonsense has caused enough pain
为这个家庭受苦
and suffering for this family.
坚持下去
Hang on.
布兰达阿姨，求你了，听我说
Aunt Brenda, please, just listen.
别烦我
Leave me alone.
在爱瑞丝的书里，她提到一个人
Okay, in Iris' book, she mentions somebody who
逃过死亡，活了下来
cheated death and survived.
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie.
来吧
Come on.
埃里克，不，等等
Eric, no, wait.
我很担心你
I'm worried about you.
阻止它
Stop it.
让我来处理这个
Let me take care of this.
来吧，鲍比
Come on, Bobby.
布伦达
Brenda.
我们走吧
Let's go.
不，不，不，你不能
No, no, no, you can't.
对不起，我不知道
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
请
Please.
你相信我，对吧？
You believe me, right?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
朱利安，我爱你
Julian, look, I love you.
但有时候我真的很恨你
But sometimes I really hate you.
我知道这一切有多令人信服
I know how convincing all of this can
是
be.
但这不是真的
But it's not real.
你怎么能这么说？
How can you say that?
我知道这些都是爱瑞丝教你的
I know Iris taught you all of this.
别让我妈的信仰毁了你的生活
Don't let my mom's beliefs derail your life
就像他们对待我一样
the same way they did mine.
非常感谢你的建议，但是
Thank you so much for that advice, but
我真的不需要妈妈了
I really don't need a mom anymore.
大开，大开
Wide open, wide.
好的，很好
All right, good.
捏一下，好吗？
Just gonna pinch, all right?
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
五，四，三
Five, four, three.
两个
Two.
好工作
Good job.
你要去夜店
You're gonna hit the club.
我需要你锁门
I need you to lock up.
别碰我的酒
And don't touch any of my liquor.
不，不，你没说要锁
No, no, you didn't say anything about locking
向上
up.
对，对，对
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你可没说要结案啊，伙计
You didn't say shit about closing, dude.
是的，把我哭成一条河
Yeah, cry me a river.
我希望你下地狱
I hope you burn in hell.
你相信这种鬼话？
You believe that shit?
我爸爸刚刚去世了
My old man just died.
我是其中的最爱
I come in as a favorite of that
混蛋，现在他想让我锁门
asshole, and now he wants me to lock
向上
up.
你知道那是什么吗？
You know what that is?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
你知道那是什么吗？
You know what that is?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
这是轻率的
It's inconsiderate.
不管怎样，你们都做完了
Anyway, you're all done.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
当然了，五星好评，对吧？
Of course, hey, five-star review, yeah?
点赞，订阅等等
Like and subscribe and all the things.
不，我不能忘记这个
No, I can't forget this
或是你离开时的面容
evening Or your face as you were leaving
但我想这就是
But I guess that's just the way the
故事是这样的，现在公平的是
story goes And now it's only fair That
我应该让你知道你应该忘记
I should let you know You should forget
或是你原来的模样
this evening Or your face as you were
离开哦,
leaving Oh,
该死
goddammit.
或者你的悲伤，是的，它应该拥抱你
Or your sorrow Yes, it should hold you
噢
Ow.
嗷,嗷
Ow, ow.
哦,他妈的
Oh, fuck.
哦
Oh.
噢
Ow.
来吧
Come on.
否
No.
好吧
Okay.
噢!
Ow!
狗屎!
Shit!
噢!
Ow!
查理，醒醒
Charlie, wake up.
查理,之后……
Charlie, wake...
查理，醒醒！
Charlie, wake up!
我整晚都在给埃里克打电话
I've been trying to call Eric all night.
他不接我电话
He's not answering me.
我不知道他在哪里
I don't know where he is.
我很担心你
I'm worried.
我相信他很好
I'm sure he's fine.
你有他的消息吗？
Well, have you heard from him?
我要去那边
I'm going over there.
我得去看看他
I need to check on him.
你也要来，查理
You're coming too, Charlie.
他转到语音信箱了
He's going to voicemail.
是他吗？
Is that him?
我朋友说纹身店被烧了
My friend just said the tattoo parlor burned
昨晚下来了
down last night.
怎么啦？
What?
史蒂芬妮!
Steph!
噢!
Ow!
哦,什么?
Oh, what?
你想杀了我？
You're trying to kill me?
埃里克?
Eric?
是啊，不，当然是你
Uh, yeah, no, of course it's you.
老兄!
Dude!
我们听说了火灾的事
We heard about the fire.
我们以为你死了
We thought you were dead.
我很好
I'm fine.
天啊，你没事吧？
Oh, my God, are you okay?
我很担心你
I was so worried about you.
是啊，一个消防员说我很幸运
Yeah, a firefighter said I was lucky as
我还穿着那件皮夹克
fuck that I was wearing that leather jacket.
它几乎没有烧伤
It barely got burned.
不过我穿着我最喜欢的夹克
I'm wearing my favorite jacket, though.
这是什么？
What is this?
哦，是的，看看
Oh, yeah, check it out.
我被打上了烙印
I got branded.
生病了,对吧?
Sick, right?
你喜欢吗？
You like it?
你说你睡着了
You said you were asleep.
不，你把我的电话打爆了
No, you were blowing up my phone like
一个该死的跟踪狂
a goddamn stalker.
你想让我做什么？
What'd you want me to do?
是啊，我不明白
Yeah, I don't get it.
你应该死了
You should be dead.
对，对，对
Right, yeah, yeah.
或者，你知道，也许……
Or, you know, maybe...
也许死亡并没有降临到我们家
Maybe death's not actually coming for our family.
因为那太他妈疯狂了
Because that would be fucking crazy.
耶稣屎!
Jesus shit!
或许我是无敌的
Or maybe I'm invincible.
埃里克?
Eric?
埃里克!
Eric!
是吗?
Yeah?
埃里克,等待
Eric, wait.
停止
Stop.
等一下，好吗？
Just wait, okay?
就因为你昨晚没死
Just because death didn't kill you last night
不代表你就安全了
doesn't mean that you're safe.
离那个修剪树机远点！
Stay away from that tree trimmer!
哦
Ooh.
要自己行动吗，斯蒂芬？
Gonna move on its own, Steph?
这就是它要做的吗？
Is that what it's gonna do?
它可能会掉下来
It could fall.
离这些孩子远点
And stay away from these kids.
我要碰碰运气
I'll take my chances.
斯蒂芬，一对孩子和一个
Steph, how is a couple kids with a
足球会杀了他吗？
soccer ball gonna kill him?
我的意思是，我不知道
I mean, I don't know.
修剪器可能会掉下来砸到树叶
The trimmer could fall and hit the leaf
吹风机的人，所以他会吹东西
blower guy, which causes him to blow stuff
打到孩子的眼睛里然后踢了一下
into the kid's eyes and then kick the
球打在他脸上
ball into his face.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
把足球扔到我脸上？
Soccer ball into my face?
这听起来确实很致命
That does sound deadly.
我应该更小心一点
I should be more careful.
嘿
Hey.
有什么事吗?
What's up?
你怎么了？
What happened to you?
显然是被死亡烤焦了
Charbroiled by death, apparently.
她来了
She came.
那真的很糟糕
That was really bad.
哦,等等
Oh, wait.
让我看看
Let me see that.
埃里克，离卡车远点
Eric, just stay away from the truck.
哦,什么?
Oh, what?
这辆卡车?
This truck?
停止
Stop.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
请
Please.
就是这辆卡车吗？
This truck right here?
但这是一辆很漂亮的卡车
But it's such a beautiful truck.
停止
Stop.
别碰它
Don't touch it.
埃里克，走开
Eric, get away.
停止
Stop.
你喜欢吗？
You like that?
你能不能…
Can you just...
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
哦
Oh.
Uh-oh.
哦，埃里克又想死了
Oh, Eric's tempted death again.
会发生什么？
What's gonna happen?
怎么啦？
What?
别再这样了
Stop doing that.
会发生什么？
What's gonna happen?
什么都没有
Nothing at all.
怎么样？
How about that?
我只是想帮你，好吗？
Look, I'm just trying to help you, okay?
试着少
Try less.
是的
Yeah.
说实话，我们受够你的垃圾了
Honestly, we're so done with your garbage.
你能不能……
Can you please...
我说了第1500遍了，没人愿意
For the 1,500th time, no one gives
你那该死的死亡诅咒
a shit about your stupid little death curse,
好吧?
okay?
所以接受暗示，别来烦我们
So take a hint and leave us alone
因为死亡不会降临到我们家
because death's not coming for our family.
茱莉亚!
Julia!
杀不死你的，只会让你更强大站起来
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger Stand
高一点不代表我寂寞
a little taller Doesn't mean I'm lonely when
我是一个人，杀不死你的东西
I'm alone What doesn't kill you makes a
把火烧高，茱莉亚！
fighter Put the fever high Julia!
不!
No!
把手给我！
Give me your hand!
我抓到你了！
I got you!
别担心，你不会是下一个！
Don't worry, you're not next!
哇,哇!
Whoa, whoa!
嘿,停止!
Hey, stop!
停!
Stop!
我妹妹在后面！
My sister's in the back!
我很抱歉，亲爱的
I'm so sorry, sweetie.
我们应该相信你的，斯蒂芬
We should have believed you, Steph.
不,我……
No, I...
我把订单搞砸了，现在轮到茱莉亚了
I screwed up the order and now Julia's
死了
dead.
是我的错
It's my fault.
伙计们,看看
Guys, look.
发生的事很痛苦，很可怕，但这
What happened was traumatic and awful, but it's
不是任何人的错
not anybody's fault.
是我的错
It's my fault.
妈，这不是你的错
Mom, it's not your fault.
这是我的错
It is my fault.
斯蒂芬妮，你只弄错了顺序
Stephanie, you were only wrong about the order
因为有些事你不知道
because there was something you didn't know.
埃里克不是霍华德的亲生儿子
Eric isn't Howard's biological son.
不好意思，你在说什么？
I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
斯蒂芬妮，我不相信你，所以我
And Stephanie, I didn't believe you, so I
我什么都没跟你说，现在我
didn't say anything to you, and now my
小女孩死了
little girl's dead.
我不明白
Well, I don't understand.
你有外遇吗？
Were you having an affair?
你父亲和我在一起
Your father and I were having such a
那段时间很艰难，但很好，因为我
hard time, but it was good because I
有你
got you.
我帮你摆脱了困境
I got you out of it.
那么谁才是真正的父亲呢？
Who's been a real dad, then?
谁是真正的父亲？
Who's been a real dad?
没关系，因为霍华德那么爱你，
It doesn't matter because Howard loved you so,
这么多
so much.
是谁？
Who is it?
谁?
Who?
谁是真正的父亲？
Who's been a real dad?
杰瑞Fenbury
Jerry Fenbury.
哦，杰瑞·芬伯里？
Oh, Jerry Fenbury?
是
Yes.
哦,狗屎
Oh, shit.
不，不，不
No, no, no, no.
他妈的杰瑞·芬伯里？
Jerry fucking Fenbury?
你不知道我们经历了什么
You don't know what we've gone through.
哦,上帝
Oh, God.
什么，这就是为什么你一直想
What, is this why you always wanted to
玩抓吗?
play catch?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
好吧
Okay.
好吧，这意味着如果它
All right, so that means that if it's
按照正确的顺序，我就是下一个
going in the right order, that I'm next,
对吧?
right?
你得帮我，斯蒂芬
You gotta help me, Steph.
妈妈，我想我做不到
Mommy, I don't think that I can.
我以为我知道，但我
I mean, I thought I did, but I
不要……
don't...
不，但是你可以
No, but you can.
我是说，你准确地预测了会发生什么
I mean, you predicted exactly what was gonna
发生
happen.
你只是把顺序搞错了，因为你
You just got the order wrong because you
我不知道所有的信息，查理
didn't have all the information, Charlie.
你说预言是什么意思？
What do you mean, predicted?
她什么都看到了
She saw everything.
修剪机，吹风机，足球
The trimmer, the blower, the soccer ball.
就像有碎片一样
Like, it was like there were pieces to
一个谜题，她必须把
a puzzle and she just had to put
他们在一起，你懂我的意思吗？
them together, you know what I mean?
这是真的吗？
Is that true?
达琳，求你了，别鼓励我这么做
Darlene, please, do not encourage this.
马蒂，我是说…
Marty, I mean...
我是说，这是爱瑞丝书里的一切
I mean, it's everything in Iris' book.
这就像一个方程
It's like an equation.
它是数学
It's math.
斯蒂芬妮，如果你能看到所有的
Stephanie, if you can see how all of
把这些联系起来，我们也许有机会
this fits together, we might have a chance.
停止
Stop.
停下来
Just stop.
你离开的时候毁了这个家，
You devastated this family when you walked out,
但没有你我们也过得很好
but we've been okay without you.
我求你不要伤害我们的孩子
I'm begging you not to traumatize our kids
了
anymore.
这次是真的
It's real this time.
我要去散步
I'm going for a walk.
我需要透透气
I need some air.
我能理解
I can appreciate that.
我们的家庭显然需要一些咨询
Our family is clearly gonna need some counseling
在未来，我们可以专注于
in the future, but can we focus on
我们都快死了的事实？
the fact that we're all about to die?
对吧?
Right?
我的意思是……
I mean...
斯蒂芬，你不是说爱瑞丝
I mean, Steph, didn't you say that Iris
认识一个死里逃生的人吗？
knew someone that cheated death or something?
是啊，是啊，嗯…
Yeah, yeah, um...
在这里的某个地方，上面写着……
In here, somewhere, it says...
就在这里，j  b  找到了一个人
that, uh, right here, J.B. found someone
谁活了下来，但上面没说什么
who survived, but it doesn't say anything about
这个j  b  是谁？
who this J.B. was or...
等一下
Wait a minute.
我知道这个名字
I know that name.
我妈妈以前经常给我写信
My mom used to write me letters, and
她有时会谈论她的一个朋友
she sometimes would talk about a friend of
她叫j  b  在一家
hers named J.B. who worked at a
医院
hospital.
医院吗?
Hospital?
呃，呃，呃，河医院
Um, um, something, uh, Something River Hospital.
呃，深河
Uh, Deep River.
和平河医院
Uh, Peace River Hospital.
呃,清晰……
Uh, Clear...
希望……
Hope...
希望河?
Hope River?
就是这样
That's it.
妈的，大概一个小时的路程
Shit, it's like an hour away.
我走了
I'm going.
我要去找他谈谈
I'm gonna go find him and talk to
我和你一起去，我自己去看他
him myself while I'm coming with you.
没关系
It's okay.
是的,是的
Yeah, yeah.
我们走吧
Let's go.
鲍比,我…
Bobby, I...
怎么啦？
What?
你得留在这里陪你妈妈
You need to stay here with your mom.
它是安全的
It's safer.
是啊，去他妈的
Yeah, fuck that.
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
我不想一个人呆在这里
I'm not staying here by myself.
在路上太危险了
Well, it's too dangerous on the road for
你
you.
你不能…
You can't...
不，我看了奶奶的死亡书，好吗？
No, I read Gammy's death book, okay?
好吧?
All right?
我是说，有上千个跟房子有关的
I mean, there's, like, a thousand house-related
死在那东西里
deaths in that thing.
伙计，你从楼梯上绊了一跤，摔倒了……
Man, you trip down the stairs, fall...
在厕所之类的地方
down a toilet or something.
我不…
I don't...
我不知道，但我不是…
I don't know, but I'm not...
我不是…
I'm not...
不行，我不会待在这里的
No way, I'm not staying here.
等一下，等一下
Hang on, hang on.
嘿,好吧
Hey, okay.
好吧,好吧
Okay, okay.
太快了
Too fast.
好吧,好吧
Okay, okay.
我们慢慢来
We'll go slow.
我去打开卡车
I'm gonna go open up the truck.
查理，去后面看看
Charlie, check the back.
明白了
Got it.
小心些而已
Be careful.
台阶有时很滑
The steps are slippery sometimes.
Oy !
Oy!
你们这些混蛋检查过坚果吗？
Any of you fuckers do a nut check?
原谅我吗?
Excuse me?
你用那玩意做了花生饼干
You made cookies in that thing with peanut
几天前刚加了黄油
butter in them just a few days ago.
这个可怜的混蛋连碰都不敢碰
This poor bastard so much as even touches
一个疯子，他的喉咙就会闭合
a nut, his throat is gonna close up
紧,…
tight and...
你理解
You understand.
花生酱在哪里？
Where's the peanut butter?
水槽上方的橱柜
Cabinet above the sink.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我很抱歉，鲍比
I'm so sorry, Bobby.
我只是…
I just...
嘿,好吧
Hey, okay.
所有清晰
All clear.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
你是个好哥哥，埃里克
You're a good brother, Eric.
螺母检查
Nut check.
怎么啦？
What?
我们走吧
Let's go.
很好
It was good.
我明白了
I get it.
我们走吧
Let's go.
来吧
Come on.
情况只会越来越糟
It's only gonna get worse.
该死的
Damn it.
等待
Wait.
我跟你一起去，兄弟
I'm coming with you, bro.
总得有人保护你
Someone's gotta protect you.
爸爸又打来了
Dad's calling again.
告诉他我们只是出去兜兜风
Tell him we just went for a ride
与妈妈
with Mom.
他不会相信的
He's not gonna believe that.
至少能给我们争取点时间
At least it'll buy us some time.
继续
Go ahead.
死亡不能给我们你的死遗嘱
Death doesn't get us your dead will.
我总是把它们放在我看得见的地方
I always keep them where I can see
他们
them.
我是说，你可以只吃真正的
I mean, you could've just had the real
东西，不过没关系
thing, but it's okay.
不是每个人都想当妈妈的
Not everyone wants to be a mom.
你是这么想的吗？
Is that what you think?
说我不想做你妈妈吗？
That I didn't want to be your mom?
听着，我是由一个女人养大的
Look, I was raised by a woman who
教会我处处看到死亡
taught me to see death everywhere.
我以为我能把这事抛诸脑后，
I thought I could put it behind me,
但当我有了你和你的
but then when I had you and your
兄弟，我只能看到一百个人
brother, all I could see were a hundred
你和查理可能会以不同的方式死去
different ways that you and Charlie could die.
我不想让你离开家
I didn't want you to leave the house.
我会被你们吓坏的
I would freak out on you guys over
什么都没有
nothing.
有一天，我看着你的脸，然后
One day, I looked at your face, and
我也看到了那个害怕的小女孩
I saw the same scared little girl that
我长大了，我知道这一点
I was growing up, and I knew that
如果我留下，会毁了你的
if I stayed, I was gonna ruin your
的生活
life.
我不知道我是不是做了
I have no idea if I did the
正确的事情
right thing.
但我现在就在你身边
But I'm here for you now.
没关系
It's okay.
我就在你后面
I'm right behind you.
嘿，谢谢，G-Buddy
Hey, thanks, G-Buddy.
我们抓住你了
We got you.
前台在这边
The front desk is this way.
哦
Oh.
嗨
Hi.
嗯…
Um...
我们在找j  b  谁是
We're looking for J.B. And who are
你吗?
you?
前台告诉我们可以找到
The front desk told us we could find
他在这里
him down here.
是你吗？
Is that you?
那就是我
That would be me.
威廉·约翰·布拉德沃斯
William John Bloodworth.
但我朋友都叫我j  b
But my friends call me J.B. I've
一直在等你，斯蒂芬妮
been waiting for you, Stephanie.
查理
Charlie.
达琳
Darlene.
但不是霍华德
But no Howard.
茱莉亚
No Julia.
那么，你们谁是下一个？
So, which one of you is next?
我…
I...
爱瑞丝的事我很遗憾
I was sorry to hear about Iris.
她是一个特别的女人
She was a special woman.
你怎么认识她的？
How did you know her?
她救了我的命
She saved my life.
什么时候?
When?
在天景酒店
At the Skyview.
我妈妈带我一起去上班
My mother brought me with her to work
那天晚上
that night.
j  b  亲爱的，我告诉过你，你得
J.B., honey, I told you, you gotta
我在台上的时候你待在后面
stay back there while I'm on stage.
我不应该在那里
I wasn't supposed to be there.
当然，除了死亡
Except, of course, to die.
别玩!
Stop playing!
所有人都得离开舞池！
Everyone needs to get off the dance floor!
下课了！
The class is about to break!
所有人现在都得下车！
Everyone needs to get off now!
等等!
Wait!
虹膜!
Iris!
你是最后一个死的
You were the last to die.
你就是那个小男孩
You were the little boy.
正确的
Correct.
所以一直以来，她都不是…
So all that time, she wasn't...
她不只是在保护我们的家庭
She wasn't just protecting our family.
她也在保护你
She was protecting you, too.
多年以后，她找到了我
Years later, she tracked me down.
帮我看清了真相
Helped me see the truth.
我们交换了想法
We traded ideas.
我帮她加固了她的船舱
I helped her fortify her cabin.
我们成了朋友
We became friends.
我甚至帮她找了最好的医生
I even helped her get the best medical
考虑到她的情况，我尽力了
care I could, considering her condition.
爱瑞丝说你找到了一个停车的人
Iris said that you found somebody who stopped
死亡和幸存
death and survived.
是
Yes.
我们怎么做呢？
And how do we do that?
只有两种方法
There are only two ways.
通过杀戮或死亡
By killing or by dying.
如果你杀了人，就会得到
If you take a life, you get the
那个人离开的时间
time that person had left.
怎么啦？
What?
否
No.
我不会杀人的
I'm not gonna kill someone.
也许我们该让他说完
Maybe we should let the guy finish.
要真正打破这个循环，你必须
Then to truly break the cycle, you have
去死
to die.
这是什么意思？
What does that mean?
很久以前，一个叫
A long time ago, a young woman named
金伯利·科曼发现自己上了死亡名单
Kimberly Corman found herself on death's list, just
喜欢你
like you.
最后轮到她的时候，她死了
And when her turn finally came, she died.
持平
Flatlined.
但她的医生把她救活了，
But her doctor managed to bring her back,
这就打破了链条
and that broke the chain.
那好吧
All right, then.
我们会这么做的
We'll do that.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
为什么爱瑞丝不试试呢？
Why didn't Iris try that?
这是有风险的
It's risky.
如果你玩弄死亡而失败，
And if you fuck with death and lose,
事情会变得非常混乱
things can get very messy.
等一下，等一下
Hang on, hang on.
好的,等待
Okay, wait.
不，肯定有别的办法
No, there has to be another way.
求你了，你得帮帮我们
Please, you have to help us.
多年来，一直有人来找我
For years, people have been coming to me
寻求建议
for advice.
嗯，我累了
Well, I'm tired.
我受够了
I'm done with all that.
现在我和爱瑞丝一样病了
And now I'm sick just like Iris.
这次不用跑了
There's no running this time.
事实是，你们都会死
Fact is, you're all gonna die.
在那之后，我也会的
And after that, I will, too.
既然我的老朋友走了，我
Now that my old friend is gone, I'm
退休
retiring.
那又怎样?
So what?
你要把我们丢在这里？
You're just gonna leave us here?
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
我打算好好享受我所拥有的时光
I intend to enjoy the time I have
离开了
left.
我建议你也这样做
And I suggest that you do the same.
生命是宝贵的
Life is precious.
享受每一秒
Enjoy every single second.
你永远不知道什么时候
You never know when.
祝你好运
Good luck.
这太棒了
That's fantastic.
否
No.
不，不可能是这个
No, that can't be it.
否
No.
这里一定有什么
There has to be something here.
肯定还有别的答案
There has to be another answer.
史蒂芬妮
Steph.
斯蒂芬，他给了我们答案
Steph, he gave us an answer.
鲍比必须死
Bobby's gotta die.
埃里克!
Eric!
你他妈的疯了吗？
Are you fucking insane?
我们不会杀鲍比的
We're not killing Bobby.
哇，哇，哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
难道只有我一个人在听吗
Am I the only guy that just listened
对那个家伙？
to that dude?
只有一个办法
There's only one way.
我们杀了鲍比，救活他，然后，
We kill Bobby, we resuscitate him, and then,
砰，你们都从死亡名单上消失了
boom, you're all off death's list.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
肯定还有别的原因，对吧？
There has to be something else, right?
我是说，肯定有别的解决办法，
I mean, there has to be another solution,
史蒂芬?
right, Steph?
否
No.
不，我们没别的办法了，好吗？
No, there's nothing else we can do, okay?
这是结束了
It's over.
我们就做完了
We'll be done.
斯蒂芬，听我说
Stephen, listen to me.
这次你得相信我，好吗？
You gotta trust me on this one, okay?
她要放弃你了
She's giving up on you.
我不会的
I'm not going to.
听着，爱瑞丝找到了阻止死亡的方法
Look, Iris found a way to hold death
关闭了几十年
off for decades.
我们也会
So will we.
我相信那家伙
I trust that guy.
你相信那家伙？
You trust that guy?
他很有趣
He was funny.
它就在那里
That just went there.
他很有魅力，你懂的
He was just oddly charismatic, and you know
我也这么认为
that as well as I do.
嗯…
Uh...
埃里克和鲍比走了
Eric and Bobby are gone.
大便
Shit.
狗屎!
Shit!
我不喜欢这样
I don't think I like this.
伙计，我们在医院里
Hey, dude, we're in a hospital.
还记得吗?
Remember?
到处都是医生
There's doctors everywhere.
我们杀了你，他们把你带回来
We kill you, they bring you back.
每个人都是安全的
Everybody's safe.
我们的英雄
We're heroes.
这和留下我完全是两码事
That is literally the opposite of keeping me
安全的
safe.
还有别的选择吗？
What's the alternative, huh?
你想杀人，然后拿走
You want to kill someone and take the
他们还剩多少时间？
time they have left?
如何?
How?
你怎么知道有多少年
How would you even know how many years
他们有什么?
they have?
否
No.
我是说，不
Well, I mean, no.
否
No.
当然不是
Of course not.
我们会这么做，对吧？
We would do that, right?
不，我们永远不会
No, we would never.
别碰那些婴儿
Don't touch those babies.
听着，底线是…
Look, bottom line...
平躺是你最好的选择
Flatlining's your best option.
你有什么好损失的？
What do you have to lose?
好吧，好吧
Okay, all right.
我们要怎么做呢？
How would we even do that?
我有个主意
Well, see, I got an idea.
但这有点疯狂
But it's a little nuts.
你的过敏是致命的，对吗？
Your allergy is deadly, right?
是的
Yeah.
嗯…
Well...
哦，嘿，伙计，等等
Oh, hey, dude, wait.
不，听着，好吗？
No, look, all right?
如果我要出去，肯定不会
If I'm going out, it's not gonna be
在这些…
on those...
这是什么？
What is it?
被侮辱的贱人，好吗？
Insulted bitches, all right?
给我
Give me those.
不错的选择
Nice choice.
哦，你在开玩笑吧
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
来吧
Come on.
嘿
Hey.
好吧
All right.
来吧
Come on.
也许这是个预兆，所以
You know, maybe this is a sign, so
我们可以…
we can just...
噢
Ow.
好吧
Okay.
伙计，也许我们现在可以走了
Hey, dude, maybe we can just bail now.
我不会放弃
I'm not giving up.
你能帮忙吗？
Can you help?
没关系的
It's all right.
我们在这里工作
We work here.
维护
Maintenance.
它很好
It's fine.
戴上你的耳机
Put your headphones back on.
伙计，它会掉下来的
Dude, it's gonna fall.
它会掉下来的
It's gonna fall.
它是下降
It's falling.
把它拿出来
Get it out.
持有它
Hold it.
它会掉下来的
It's gonna fall.
简单的工作
Easy work.
现在怎么办呢?
Now what?
跟我来
Come with me.
这是……
It's...
嘿，等一下
Hey, hang here.
我得找点东西
I gotta get something.
怎么啦？
What?
不要动
Don't move.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
不,那是……
No, that's...
那很酷
That's cool.
我搜查了浴室
I searched the bathrooms.
他们不在房车里？
They weren't in the RV?
否
No.
如果埃里克想杀鲍比，
Look, if Eric was trying to kill Bobby,
他们会在哪里？
where would they be?
我不知道，但有很多方法
I don't know, but there's a million ways
死在医院里
to die in a hospital.
我能帮你吗？
Can I help you?
原谅我吗?
Excuse me?
不，我只是来看我奶奶
No, uh, just came to see my Nana.
嗨,格拉迪斯
Hi, Gladys.
在这里
Here.
今天天气真好
Lovely day today.
还有时间吗？
Got much time left?
我想是的
I think so.
所有可能相互作用的金属物品和设备
All metallic belongings and devices that could interact
用核磁共振成像的强力磁铁
with the MRI's powerful magnet.
伙计，查理打电话来了
Hey, uh, dude, Charlie's trying to call.
我不关心这个
I don't care about that.
好吧，来吧
Okay, come on.
坐下来
Sit down.
坐，坐，坐，坐
Sit, sit, sit, sit.
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
否
No.
坐在那里
Sit in that.
我有个好主意
I've got a great idea.
好吧
Okay.
走廊尽头有个急诊室，所以
There's an ER down the hall, so as
一旦你的线变平，砰
soon as you flatline, boom.
我要把你推下去，伙计
I'm gonna wheel your ass down, man.
他们会把你带回来的
They're gonna bring you right back.
嘿，你的肾上腺素笔呢？
Hey, where's your EpiPen?
呃，就在这儿
Uh, it's right here.
把它给我
Give it to me.
为什么?
Why?
那是什么？
What is that?
伙计
Dude.
给你
Give it.
老兄,听
Dude, listen.
整个想法就是你必须这么做
The whole idea is that you have to
死
die.
还记得吗?
Remember?
这能让你活下去
This keeps you alive.
现在坐
Now sit.
伙计，我们得快点了
Dude, we need to hurry.
来吧，走吧
Come on, go.
好吧
All right.
好了，吃吧
All right, eat up.
嘿,男人
Hey, man.
计划很好，但是，如果
The plan's great, but, you know, if it
行不通……
doesn't work out...
会成功的，鲍比
It's going to work, Bobby.
是的
Yeah.
是啊，但是，以防万一
Yeah, but, you know, just in case, and
我真的死了……
I die for real...
你能不能…
Will you just, um...
你会照顾帕科吗？
Will you look after Paco?
是的，是的，当然
Yeah, yeah, of course.
我会照顾他的
I'll look after him.
伙计，我只是说说而已
Dude, I'm just saying.
我是说，海龟活下来就像
I mean, the turtles live to be like
100岁了，而且……
100 years old, and...
我不会花时间去承诺
I'm not gonna take time for commitment.
看着我
Look at me.
兄弟，我不会照顾帕科的
Brother, I'm not gonna take care of Paco
因为你会没事的
because you are gonna be okay.
我和你，我们会解决的
Me and you, we are going to fix
现在每个人的东西
things for everyone right now.
我保证，我不会让你得逞的
I promise you, I'm not gonna let you
死
die.
严格来说，我会让你死，但是
Technically, I'm gonna let you die, but then
我会把你带回来的
I'm gonna bring you back.
老兄，这一点都不好笑
Dude, it's not funny.
我只是在跟你开玩笑
I'm just fucking with you.
来吧
Come on.
你能行的
You got this.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
怎么啦？
What?
真的很好吃
It's really good.
这很好，我知道
It's very good, I know.
那又怎样，除了好，还有什么
So what, okay, other than good, what are
你感觉怎么样?
you feeling?
什么都没有
Nothing.
你在开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
怎么，你是说你不再过敏了吗？
What, you're telling me you're not allergic anymore?
我不知道，伙计
I don't know, man.
太完美了
That's just perfect.
我的头发长出来了
My hair grew out of it.
它长出了什么？
What grew out of it?
他妈的
Fuck.
你知道，我没有备用计划
You know, I don't have a plan B
完全正确
exactly.
嘿，你成功了
Hey, you're doing it.
对，对，对，你在做
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're doing it.
鲍比，你做到了
Bobby, you're doing it.
嘿，我和你在一起
Hey, I'm here with you.
我和你在一起
I'm here with you.
嘿，嘿，我不能给你这个
Hey, hey, I can't give you that.
嘿
Hey.
鲍比,鲍比
Bobby, Bobby.
嘿
Hey.
请
Please.
鲍比，这都是计划的一部分
Bobby, this is all part of the plan.
冷静点
Just calm down.
鲍比，坐在轮椅上
Bobby, in the wheelchair.
试着再给他们打电话
Try calling them again.
这是我们唯一能做的
This is the only way we can do
这一点
this.
不!
No!
他妈的!
Fuck!
快跑!
Run!
我的天啊
Oh my God.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
是的
Yeah.
不!
No!
如果艾瑞克没有血缘关系，他为什么会死
Why is Eric dead if he's not related
虹膜?
to Iris?
当你和死亡打交道时，事情就会变得一团糟
When you fuck with death, things get messy.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
不安全
It's not safe.
然后去哪里？
Then go where?
没有地方是安全的
Nowhere is safe.
除了爱瑞丝的小屋
Except Iris' cabin.
她在那里生存了几十年
She was able to survive there for decades.
然后她的脸就被炸掉了
And then she got her face blown off.
她是因为离开小屋才死的
She only died because she left the cabin.
外面很危险，但里面是最安全的
Outside is dangerous, but inside is the safest
有个地方
place that there is.
你是对的
You're right.
这是我们唯一有
It's the only place where we have any
的优势
advantage.
所以我们就把自己锁在小屋里
So we just lock ourselves in a cabin
到永远吗?
forever?
不是你
Not you.
我
Me.
妈妈，你不能走
Mom, you can't leave.
我们刚把你找回来
We just got you back.
如果有人要住在那间小屋里，那就是我
If anybody's gonna live in that cabin, it's me.
只要我还活着，
And as long as I am alive,
死亡不能伤害你
death can't touch you.
-妈妈  -让我来
-Mom. -Let me do this.
他不会让你一个人去的
He'll never let you get there on your own.
但我能看到他来了
But I can see him coming.
我们必须共同努力
We have to do this together.
好吧
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你应该开车
You should drive.
是的
Yeah.
天呐
Holy shit.
看看这个地方
Look at this place.
我不可能熬过去的
It's gonna be impossible to get through that
门
gate.
他要行动了
He's about to make a move.
我不知道那是什么
I don't know what it is.
我们得马上把你弄进去
We need to get you inside now.
等待
Wait.
等等,什么?
Wait, what?
好了，我们进去吧
Okay, let's get inside.
大便
Shit.
怎么啦？
What?
我可以帮忙
I can help.
不要等我
Don't wait for me.
进去吧
Just get inside.
斯蒂芬，如果你进去，我就安全了
Steph, if you get inside, I'll be safe.
走了
Go.
好吧
Okay.
来吧
Come on.
妈妈?
Mom?
妈妈!
Mom!
妈妈?
Mom?
别为我担心
Don't worry about me.
去救你妹妹吧
Go save your sister.
我要活下去，只要
I'm gonna stay alive as long as-
我的天啊
Oh my god.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
简单呼吸就好
Just breathe.
呼吸
Breathe.
查理，发生什么事了？
Charlie, what happened?
你是好的
You're okay.
你死了，我把你救活了
You died, and I brought you back.
你把我带回来了
You brought me back.
我们现在安全了
We're safe now.
妈妈?
Mom?
否
No.
她救了我们
She saved us.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
好了，我准备好了
All right, I'm ready.
他来了
Well, there he is.
哇
Wow.
好吧,查理
Okay, Charlie.
好吧，让我们转一圈
All right, give us a spin.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
哦
Oh.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
你看起来真不错
You look really good.
我有一个很棒的发型师
I have a great stylist.
快点，我们要迟到了
Come on, we'll be late.
珍妮在哪里?
Where's Jenny?
我想她还在里面准备着
I think she's still inside getting ready.
来，我来修一下
Here, let me fix this.
我真的很高兴你能来
I'm really happy you could be here for
这一点
this.
我也是
Me too.
哦
Oh.
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
请给我一块饼干好吗？
Can I have one cookie, please?
查理
Charlie.
看，它很锋利
Look, it's sharp.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
斯蒂芬，我想让你见见珍妮的爸爸，
Steph, I want you to meet Jenny's dad,
Reddick博士
Dr. Reddick.
嘿
Hey.
嗨
Hi.
见到你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
你也一样
You too.
我们只是崇拜查理
We just adore Charlie.
我知道他是个救星
And I understand he's quite the lifesaver.
是啊，你听说了
Oh, yeah, you heard about that.
他让我起死回生了
He, uh, brought me back from the dead.
嗯?
Hmm?
是的
Yeah.
怎么啦？
What?
严格来说，你没死
Well, technically, you weren't dead.
怎么啦？
What?
我是说，如果你不省人事，而查理
I mean, if you were unconscious and Charlie
让你再次呼吸，然后你的心脏停止了
got you breathing again, then your heart didn't
停止
stop.
不管怎样，干得好，查理
But regardless, way to go, Charlie.
这么说她没死？
So she wasn't dead?
完全正确
Exactly.
她很幸运查理在那里
She was lucky Charlie was there.
是的，任何事情的发生都有原因
Yep, everything happens for a reason.
珍妮!
Jenny!
亲爱的，你看起来棒极了
Sweetie, you look like a million bucks.
天啊，好险啊
Oh my god, that was close.
你没事吧?
You okay?
-是的  -哦
-Yeah. -Oh.